conceptronic.net 2018-05-10

# Conceptronic

We (the company Digital Data Communications GmbH) take the protection of your personal data very seriously and strictly adhere to the rules of data protection laws. Personal information is only collected on this website where technically necessary. In no case will this information be sold or otherwise transferred to third parties. The following statement provides an overview of how we guarantee this protection, what kind of data is collected and for what purpose. 

1\. Data processing on this website 

Digital Data Communications GmbH automatically collects and saves logfile information in your server, which your browser transmits to us. Data collected include: 

\- Browser type and version 

\- Operating system 

\- Referrer URL (the previously visited website)

\- Host name of accessing computer (IP address)

\- Time of the sever request.

Digital Data Communications GmbH cannot assign these data to specific individuals. These data is not combined with data from other sources. Moreover, after statistical analysis, data are deleted. 

2\. Cookies 

Websites use cookies in different places. Cookies serve to make our services more user-friendly, effective and secure. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and saved by your browser. Most of the cookies we use are known as "session cookies". They are automatically deleted after your visit. Cookies do not harm your computer and do not contain viruses. 

3\. Use of Social Media Plugins 

a) We are currently using the following social media plug-ins: Facebook, Twitter, Google+, Xing, T3N, LinkedIn, Flattr. We use the so-called two-click solution. This means that if you visit our site, initially no personal data will be passed on to the providers of these plug-ins. The provider of the plug-in can be identified by the marking on the greyed out box using the first letter. Only when you press one of the plug-ins, personal data will be transferred. By activating the plug-in, data is automatically transmitted to the respective plug-in provider and stored there (US providers in the USA). We have no influence on the data collected and processing operations; we are not aware of the full scope of data collection, purposes and retention periods. Since the plug-in provider carries out the data collection, in particular via cookies, we recommend you to delete all cookies before clicking on the grayed-out box via the security setting of your browser. 

b) Through the integration of a plug-in, the plug-in provider receives the information that you have accessed a specific page of our online offer. Furthermore, the following data are transmitted (IP address, date and time of the request, time zone difference to the Greenwich Meantime, content of the request (concrete page), access status / http status code, amount of data transferred, request source website, browser, Operating system and interface, language and version of the browser software). When using Facebook and Xing, according to the provider in Germany, only anonymized IP addresses are loaded. This is done whether or not you have an account with this plug-in provider or you are logged in. If you are logged in to the plug-in provider, these data will be assigned directly to your account. When activating the Activated Button and link the page, for example, the plug-in provider also stores this information in your user account and communicates this to your contacts in public. If you do not want to have the assignment in your profile with the plug-in provider, you must log out before activating the button. 

c) The plug-in provider stores these data as user profiles and uses them for purposes of advertising, market research and / or the customized design of its site. Such evaluation is also made for users who are not logged in, to display customized advertising and to inform other users of the social network about activities on our website. You have a right to object to the creation of these user profiles. You must contact the respective plug-in provider to exercise this right. 

d) For more information on the purpose and extent of the data collection and its processing by the plug-in provider, please refer to the privacy statements of these providers provided below. Here you will also find further information on your rights and settings options for protecting your privacy. Addresses of the respective provider and URL with their privacy notices: 

\- Facebook Inc., 1601 S California Avenue, Palo Alto, California 94304, USA; https://www.facebook.com/policy.php and http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other#applications

\- Twitter Inc., 1355 Market St., Suite 900, San Francisco, California 94103, USA; https://twitter.com/privacy 

\- Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountainview, California 94043, USA; https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/?hl=de 

\- Xing AG, Dammtorstrasse 30 20354 Hamburg, DE; http://www.xing.com/privacy 

\- T3N, yeebase media GmbH, Kriegerstr. 40, 30161 Hanover, Germany; https://t3n.de/store/page/datenschutz 

\- LinkedIn Corporation, 2029 Stierlin Court, Mountain View, California 94043, United States; http://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy 

\- Flattr Network Ltd. Based in 2nd Floor, White bear yard 114A, Clerkenwell Road, London, Middlesex, England, EC1R 5DF, United Kingdom; https://www.flattr.com/privacy 

e) Third Parties Services inclusion

We have included YouTube videos in our online offering, which are stored on http://www.YouTube.com and are directly playable from our website. These are all integrated in the "Extended Privacy Mode", ie no data about you as user are transferred to Youtube if you do not play the videos. Furthermore, the following data are transferred: IP address, date and time of the request, time zone difference to the Greenwich Meantime, content of the request (concrete page), access status / http status code, amount of data transferred, request source website, browser, Operating system and interface, language and version of the browser software. We have no influence on this data transfer. 

4\. Newsletter

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we need your e-mail address and the confirmation that you are the owner of the given e-mail address and that you agree to receive the newsletter. This information is collected for the sole purpose of being able to send the newsletter to you and to document our permission to send it. Your data will not be disclosed to third parties. The order of the newsletter and your consent to store the e-mail.- Address can be revoked at any time. 

5\. Web Portal and Web Shop

If you want to use our portal and web shop, you need to register. You need to provide the mandatory information, for registration purposes. Optional information is voluntary. The terms of use and requirements for registration as dealer and as certified reseller can be found in the General Terms and Conditions. When creating an account below**, your stored data will be revocably saved. You can always delete the account in the customer area. Moreover, we set a personal username and password: your username and password will ensure that you have sole access to your profile - therefore, you should never make your password available to any third party. Your password can not be seen by us, it is stored in an encrypted form in a database.

If you use our portal, we store your data necessary for the fulfillment of the contract, as well as information about payment method. Furthermore, we will store the optional data provided by you for the time you use the portal, unless you delete them before. 

In order to prevent unauthorized access by third parties to your personal data, in particular financial data, the ordering process is encrypted using SSL technology.

6\. Contact form

When dealing with requests done via the contact form, we only collect the data necessary to process your request. Specification of further data is voluntary. The data will only be used to process your request and will not be shared with third parties. Data entered via the contact form will not be used for promotional purposes. After processing your request your data will be deleted. You can revoke your consent of processing your data at any time via the address provided in the imprint.

7\. Google Maps

This website uses the product Google Maps by Google Inc. Hereto, corresponding map content is retrieved from the servers of Google. By using Google Maps, information about your use of the website (including the IP address) may be transmitted and stored to a Google server in the United States. **We reference to the privacy notices of Google (http://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy/) and the terms of use of Google Maps (https://www.google.com/intl/de_de/help /terms_maps.html).

8\. Right to information 

You have, at any time, the right to obtain information of the stored data concerning your person, including source and recipients of the data, as well as the purpose of data processing. Please direct your request in writing or by e-mail to our above address, or to our data protection officer at datenschutz@agad.de.

9\. Additional Information

Your trust is important to us. This means we are happy to talk to you at any time and to answer questions regarding the processing of your personal data. If you have any questions that could not be answered by this privacy policy, or if you want more in-depth information on a point, please contact the data protection officer at datenschutz@agad.de at any time. 

This Privacy Policy applies exclusively to content on our servers and does not include the websites linked to our site.
